http://www.experienceneworleans.com/gdpr-privacy-statement.html

Broadway
Say What?
New Orleans Cemeteries
Cajuns & Creoles
Voodoo
Bring N.O. New Orleans Home
Shop in New Orleans!
Recipes
Book Your Stay!
Adults:
1
2
3
4
Rooms:
Experience New Orleans
Experience New Orleans (“The Controllers”) collect personal data from individual users of www.experienceneworleans.com – this is collected through our newsletter when you sign up and is only used to send a newsletter once monthly. Data (such as IP addresses) is also collected by Google Analytics to track the number of users, pages viewed, etc.. Certain elements of this data may constitute protected “personal data” as that term is defined in the E.U. General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”)*.
The following disclosures concerning The Controllers’ compliance with GDPR are presented for informational and compliance purposes only.  Nothing in these disclosures constitutes a representation that any particular data or service is governed or subject to GDPR, nor do these disclosures represent or constitute any contract or undertaking with any individual.
Effective Date of GDPR
GDPR took effect on May 25, 2018.    The Controllers will comply with GDPR to the extent applicable.
Utilization of Data
The Controllers utilize personal data including the information provided by you during usage of the website and submission of forms.  The Controllers process this data for to send you information electronically or physically that you request.
Basis for the Processing of Data
The Controllers may seek your consent to send communications (marketing communications by newsletter) in certain cases which may be revoked by you at any time via email to lori@compucast.com or by clicking unsubscribe on the pertinent email communication.
Recipients of Personal Data
Recipients of personal data may include staff for physical mailing, email newsletters, technical providers of data storage, and back-end service providers.  All employees of The Controllers who receive or review personal data have received training concerning maintaining the confidentiality of such data and committed themselves to confidentiality.  Where appropriate, The Controllers will enter into written agreements governing the processing and confidentiality of personal data by third parties.
Storage of Data
The Controllers will retain data only as long as is necessary.
Your Rights Under GDPR
If the GDPR applies to retention of your personal data, you have several rights including (i) the right to request access, rectification or erasure of your data, (ii) the right to lodge a complaint with the appropriate European Union supervisory authority, and (iii) to the extent processing of data is based on consent, you have the right.
Please visit eugdpr.org for more information.
Sign up for our mailing list to receive information on the latest New Orleans news, events, and attractions!
Join Now!
designed by Compucast Web, Inc.
We serve cookies to analyze traffic and customize content on this site.
Privacy Policy / GDPR - EU
Got it!
We serve cookies to analyze traffic and customize content on this site.
Privacy Policy / GDPR - EU
Got it!
